Is organic food worth the higher price?
有机食品值得花更高的价钱吗？
It’s the classic grocery store dilemma.
这是在杂货店购物时常见的两难选择。
On the one hand, your family dinner table deserves only the best.
一方面，你家的餐桌理应只摆最好的食物。
On the other hand, your wallet can only stretch so far.
另一方面，你的钱包能承受的却很有限。
Whether or not to buy organic is a personal decision, said Mike von Massow, professor of Food, Agricultural and Resource Economics.
食品、农业与资源经济学教授迈克·冯·马索说，买不买有机食品是个人的决定。
Science won’t give a clear-cut answer to the question of whether organic food is “better.”
对于有机食品是否“更好”这个问题，科学不会给出明确的答案。
There are often trade-offs, and answers become less definitive depending on the product under consideration.
这其中常常需要权衡取舍，而且答案也会因所考虑的产品不同而变得不那么确定。
One thing is definitive: Organic and conventionally grown food are equally nutritious.
有一点是确定的：有机食品和常规种植的食品营养价值相同。
From a nutrition point of view, there is no difference between organic and traditionally grown products.
从营养角度看，有机产品和传统种植的产品没有区别。
Organic products don’t necessarily have fewer pesticides—in fact, they may have more.
有机产品上的农药残留不一定更少——事实上，可能还更多。
There is also no big difference between organic and non-organic products from a food-safety perspective.
从食品安全角度看，有机产品和非有机产品之间也没有太大差别。
Even organic growers use pesticides.
就连有机种植者也使用农药。
Testing shows little if any pesticide remains on conventionally grown products.
检测表明，常规种植的产品上即便有农药残留，也微乎其微。
In fact, organic farmers often use larger quantities of pesticide because they can only use the natural variety of insect-killers.
事实上，有机农场主的农药用量往往更大，因为他们只能使用天然的杀虫剂。
Chemical pesticides generally kill a much wider range of pests than any single natural pesticide.
化学农药能杀灭的害虫范围通常比任何一种天然农药都要广得多。
The use of animal waste in organic agriculture can also be a factor in the spread of bacteria like E. coli and salmonella.
有机农业中使用动物粪便，也可能是导致大肠杆菌、沙门氏菌等细菌传播的一个因素。
Over the past 10 years, Canada has seen more food-safety recalls for organic products, proportionally, than for conventional products.
过去10年间，按比例计算，加拿大有机产品因食品安全问题被召回的次数比常规产品更多。
On the whole, organic agriculture may have a smaller environmental footprint.
总体而言，有机农业对环境的影响可能更小。
That’s mostly because the risk of groundwater contamination from organic farming is lower.
这主要是因为有机耕作造成地下水污染的风险更低。
Organic farmers have never used neonics, the controversial pesticides that have been linked to shrinking bee populations worldwide.
有机农场主从未使用过新烟碱类农药，这类农药颇具争议，被认为与全球蜜蜂数量减少有关。
Traditional agriculture has been making “dramatic improvements” to reduce its impact on the environment.
为了减少对环境的影响，传统农业一直在做出“重大改进”。
It isn’t a black-and-white picture, though.
不过，情况并非非黑即白。
Organic farming is much less efficient when it comes to land use, although yields vary considerably depending on the crop.
在土地利用方面，有机耕作的效率要低得多，不过产量因作物不同而差异相当大。
On the other hand, advocates of organic farming argue yields and efficiency could be significantly improved if the food industry devoted as much research and money to organic farming as it does to conventional agriculture.
另一方面，有机农业的倡导者认为，如果食品行业像对常规农业那样，向有机农业投入同样多的研究和资金，其产量和效率可能会大幅提高。